几个世纪以来 圣殿骑士团都在寻找着神秘的伊甸苹果
For centuries, the order of the Knights Templar have searched for the mythical Apple of Eden.
他们相信它不光包含着
They believe it contains not only
人类第一次反抗的种子
the seeds of man's first disobedience,
还有自由意志的关键
but the key to the free will itself.
如果他们找到遗物并解开其中的秘密
If they find the relic and decode its secrets,
他们将获得掌控一切自由思想的力量
they will have the power to control all freedom of thought.
只有刺客兄弟会在阻止他们
Only the brotherhood called the Assassins stands in their way...
安达卢西亚 西班牙 1492年
ANDALUCIA, SPAIN 1492
宗教法庭最终还是把西班牙交给了圣殿骑士
The Inquisition has finally delivered Spain to the Templars.
苏丹穆罕穆德和他的人仍然坚守在格拉纳达
Sultan Muhammad and his people still hold out in Granada.
但如果他的儿子 王子 被抓住了
But if his son, the prince, is captured,
他将投降并交出伊甸苹果
he will surrender the city and the Apple of Eden.
你阿吉拉尔·德·内尔哈是否
Do you, Aguilar de Nerha,
发誓在捍卫自由的战斗中 让我们的信条荣耀?
swear to honor our order in the fight for freedom?
守护人类抵抗圣殿骑士的暴政
To defend mankind against Templars' tyranny,
并且保护自由意志?
and preserve free will?
我发誓
I swear.
如果伊甸苹果落入他们之手
If the Apple falls into their hands,
圣殿骑士将摧毁 挡在他们面前的一切
the Templars will destroy everything that stands in their way.
抗议异议和我们 为自己着想的权利
Protest, dissent, our right to think for ourselves.
向我发誓 你将牺牲自己的性命
Swear to me that you will sacrifice your life
和在场所有人的性命 来防止神器落入他们手中
and lives of everyone here to keep it from them.
是的导师
Yes, Mentor.
我们的生命无关紧要
Our lives are nothing.
伊甸苹果才是一切
The Apple is everything.
雄鹰的英灵 将看守未来
The spirit of the Eagle, will watch over the future.
其他人盲目 追寻真理的时候
Where other men blindly follow the truth,
记住万事皆虚
remember, nothing is true.
当其他人被 道德法律束缚时
Where other men are limited by morality or law,
记住事事皆允
remember, everything is permitted.
我们在黑暗中为光明服务
We work in the darkness to serve the light.
我们是刺客
We are Assassins.
下加利福尼亚 墨西哥 1986年
Baja California, Mexico 1986
该死
Shit.
妈妈?
Mom?
爸爸?
Dad?
你的血不只属于你自己卡尔
Your blood is not your own, Cal.
他们找到我们了
They've found us.
活在阴影里
Live in the shadows.
逃!快逃!
Go! Go now!
30年后
30 YEARS LATER
亨茨维尔监狱 德克萨斯州美国
HUNTSVILLE PENITENTIARY, TEXAS, USA
你是来这拯救我的灵魂的吧
You're here to save my soul.
差不多把
Something like that.
我
I...
我知道今天是你生日
I understand it is your birthday.
对的
Yeah.
派对刚刚开始
The party is just getting started.
坐下你让我紧张
Sit down. You're making me nervous.
主啊
Lord,
清洗我的罪恶
wash away my sin,
我将再次
and I'll be clean...
变干净
Once again.
你不是个信徒对吧?
You're not much for the Bible, are you?
特告知 卡勒姆·林奇
Be it known that Callum Lynch
被认定犯一级谋杀罪
has been found guilty of capital murder
被判于今日执行死刑 2016年10月21日
and sentenced to die on this day, October 21st 2016.
犯人想做最后陈述么?
Does the prisoner wish to make a final statement?
告诉我父亲咱们地狱见
Tell my father that I'll see him in hell.
我的名字是索菲亚·莱金博士
My name is Dr. Sophia Rikkin.
昨天傍晚6点 你 被处决并宣告死亡
At six pm yesterday evening, you were executed and pronounced dead.
到现在为止 如人们所知
And so far, as anyone in the world knows or cares,
你不再存在
you no longer exist.
你最好坐着
It's better you to sit.
我的眼睛
My eyes...
你现在感觉不舒服但很正常
What are you feeling right now is normal and uncomfortable.
卡尔
Cal.
我是来帮你的
I'm here to help you.
你也要帮我
And you're here to help me.
别管它
Let him go.
别碰他
Don't touch him.
继续啊跳下去
Go ahead. Do it.
跳啊
Jump.
在这你不是囚犯卡尔
You're not a prisoner here, Cal.
我是来保护你的
I'm here to protect you.
如果你听我的一切都说得通
If you listen to me, everything is going to make sense.
你要相信我
And you need to trust me.
我在哪儿?
Where am I?
你在阿布斯泰戈基金会 马德里的康复区里
You're in a rehabilitation wing of Abstergo Foundation in Madrid,
一个致力于完善人类的私人组织
a private organization dedicated to the perfection of human kind.
有了你的帮助 我们能开发出消除暴力的新方法
With your help, we can pioneer new ways to eradicate violence.
我能搞定
I had this.
你父亲想要抓住它
Your father wants him in.
他是我的病人
He's my patient.
这是我的项目
This is my program.
准备好Animus
Prepare the Animus.
袖剑准备好了吗?
Are the blades prepared?
在这
Right here.
找到来源了么?
And we confirmed their provenance?
属于阿吉拉尔
They belong to Aguilar.
我们在他的埋葬处找到它们的
We recovered them from his burial site.
这些是什么玩意儿?
What are these?
执行最后准备 我们的回归点是安达卢西亚1492年
Assume final preparations. Our regression, Andalucía, 1492.
把所有都记录下来
Record everything.
机械手臂准备完毕
Arms ready.
这是要干嘛?
What is this?
真不好意思卡尔这不是我做事的风格
I'm sorry, Cal, this is not the way I like to do things.
那就别这样
Then don't do it.
注入硬脊膜外麻醉剂
Insert epidural.
你到底想从我这得到什么?
What do you want from me?
你的过去
Your past.
仔细听我讲卡尔
Listen to me carefully, Cal.
你马上就要进入Animus
You're about to enter the Animus.
你将见到的听到的和感受到的
What you are about to see, hear and feel,
都是某个死去500年的人的记忆
are the memories of someone who has been dead for 500 years.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你改变不了发生的事卡尔
You can't change what happens, Cal.
启动扫描仪
Engage scanner.
状态?
Status?
正在扫面DNA链 正在寻找时间框架
Scanning DNA chains. Searching for time frame.
已锁定首段匹配记忆
First memory match locked.
已识别DNA匹配
DNA match identified.
坚持住卡尔
Stay with it, Cal.
尝试同步
Attempt synchronization.
我们找到他了 我们找到阿吉拉尔了
We found him. We found Aguilar.
已获得同步
Synchronization achieved.
就这样
There.
执行回归
Commence regression.
我们的目标是那个男孩
Our mission is the boy.
他就是王子
It's the prince.
是谁家庇护那个男孩的?
Which household harbored the boy?
就我一个
Only me.
没人知道没人
Nobody else knew. Nobody.
把他全家吊死给他看
Hang his family and make him watch.
烧了整个村子
Burn the whole village.
格拉纳达的王子被抓住了 他父亲苏丹
With the prince of Granada as captive, his father, sultan,
将交出他的反叛城市
will surrender his rebellious city,
异教徒最后的庇护所
the last safe haven for the infidels.
上帝会惩罚他手下的异端
God will punish his people's heresy.
最终西班牙将被圣殿骑士统治
Finally Spain will be under one Templar rule.
紧盯着记忆卡尔
Stay with the memory, Cal.
阿吉拉尔!那个男孩阿吉拉尔! 那个男孩!
Aguilar! The boy, Aguilar! The boy!
那个男孩阿吉拉尔!
Aguilar, the boy!
把他拉出来!
Pull him!
执行恢复
Commence rehabilitation.
检查一下系统 记录他的状态
Run a system's check, and log his condition.
干的不错卡尔
You did well, Cal.
回首过去 很明显
Looking back it's clear that a history
世界历史就是暴力的历史
of the world is history a violence.
去年反社会行为带来的经济损失
Last year the economic impact of antisocial behavior
高达9万亿美元
was 9 trillion dollars.
我们相信现在一个人找不到合适的出路时
We believe that man today experiences
就会采取一定的暴力
a measure of aggression which he finds no acceptable outlets.
现在想象一下如果将 这些花费引导到其他地方
Now imagine if all these costs could be channeled elsewhere...
回归进行得好吗?
So the regression went well?
就是林奇
Lynch is the one.
阿吉拉尔的直系后裔
Direct descendent of Aguilar.
一切都非常清晰 这还是头一次
Everything was clear in there, for the first time.
我们都梦寐以求的是什么? 一个更和平的世界
What do we all dream of? A more peaceful world.
你又抢了我的台词
I see you stole my lines again.
我只抢最好的
I only steal from the best.
神器呢?
And the artifact?
伊甸苹果 它就在我们掌控之中
The Apple. It's within our grasp.
发生了什么? 为什么把他拉出来?
What happened in there? Why did you pull him?
我必须这样 我们必须保持他的健康
I had to. We have to keep him healthy.
获得他的信任 我知道他会把我们引向神器的
Earn his confidence. And I know he'll lead us to it.
逼他一把
Push him.
Animus这不是这样工作的
That's not how the Animus works.
搞定了
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
1917年卢瑟福分裂了原子
1917 Rutherford splits the atom.
1953年沃森和克里克 发现了DNA双螺旋
1953 Watson and Crick find a double helix.
2016年我的女儿
2016 my daughter
找到了治疗暴力的方法
finds the cure for violence.
你总比我更聪明
You've always been brighter than me.
我迟到了
I'm late.
我要向长老汇报
I have to report to the Elders.
弗朗西斯科·利兹的 《伟大宗教法庭》1492年
Francisco Rizi's Grand Inquisition. 1492.
战争 宗教的控告
War, religious prosecution,
托尔克马达神父或 任何我们组织的人
and the closest that Father Torquemada or any of our Order
最接近找到伊甸苹果的一次
came to a finding the Apple of Eden.
你最近怎么样我的朋友?
How are you, my friend?
还好
Well.
阁下
Your Excellency.
下周长老见面时
Next week when the Elders meet,
我们将投票结束你的 阿布斯泰戈计划
we shall vote to discontinue your Abstergo project.
我们觉得每年给你的300万
We feel that giving you 3 billion annually,
能花在更好的地方
could be better spent elsewhere.
3百万算不了什么
Tri billion is nothing compared to...
我们赢了
We've won.
人们不再关注他们的公民自由
People are no longer care about their civil liberties,
他们在乎自己的生活标准
they care about their standard of life.
现代世界已经不再需要自由之类的观念
The modern world has outgrown notions like freedom.
他们满足于遵守
They are content to follow.
只要自由意志存在 威胁就存在
The threat remains while free will exists.
几个世纪以来我们尝试用 宗教、政治和现在的消费主义
For centuries we try with religion, with politics and now consumerism
来消除异议
to eliminate dissent.
难道不是时候来试一下科学吗?
Isn't it the time we gave a science a try?
我的女儿比我们以往更接近目标
My daughter is closer than we've ever been.
你漂亮的女儿怎么样了?
How is your beautiful daughter?
她追踪到了伊甸苹果的保护者
She has traced protectors of the Apple.
在哪儿?
Where?
安达卢西亚1492年
Andalucía, 1492.
后裔呢?
The descendents?
所有血脉都消亡了
All the blood lines have died out.
除了一个
But one.
我们已经追踪了他过去的的五百年 追踪到了刺客兄弟会
We've traced his back 500 years, to the Assassin's Brotherhood.
你的幻觉我们称之为“出血效应”
Hallucinations are what we call the "bleeding effect."
你过去的影像
Images of your regression,
出现在你现在的视野里
laying themselves over your present day field of vision.
如果你允许 我能教你怎么控制它们
If you allow me, I can teach you how to control them.
退下都早我掌握中
Stand down. I have this.
别管他们
Let it be.
这到底是什么? 那个机器是干什么的?
What is it? The machine?
这是基因记忆
It's genetic memory.
通过Animus
By using the Animus,
我们能再历那些造就我们的人的生活
we can relive lives of those who made us who we are.
我在那里见到的 感觉像真的
What I saw in there, it felt real.
就是真的
It was.
从某方面来说
In a way.
别惹我!
Don't mess with me!
我感觉不一样了
I feel different now.
干嘛这么激动?
Why the aggression?
我就是个冲动的人
I'm an aggressive person.
这到底是什么监狱?
What kind of prison is this?
这不是监狱卡尔
It's not a prison, Cal.
如果你合作的话你能学到更多
You'll learn more if you cooperate.
放开我
Let me go.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
跟我来
Come with me.
林奇 1979年-现在
LYNCH 1979-present
这是什么?
What is this?
我知道你的一切卡尔
I know everything about you, Cal.
你的医疗记录 你的心理档案
Your medical data, your psychological profile,
你MAO-A基因里的变异
the mutations in your MAO-A gene.
我知道你的寄养家庭
I know about the foster homes.
你的青少年收容所
The juvenile homes.
你是遗传和暴力之间关联的活例子
You are a living proof of the link between heredity and crime.
你怎么找到我的?
How did you find me?
我们找到了阿吉拉尔
We found Aguilar.
你被捕时你的DNA和他匹配
When you were arrested, your DNA matched his.
- 阿吉拉尔是谁? - 你的祖先
- Who is Aguilar? - Your ancestor.
他的家族都是刺客
His family were Assassins.
他们被圣殿骑士、托尔克马达
They were burnt at the stake by the Templars,
和你看到的那个黑骑士 奥赫达烧死在刑柱上
Torquemada and the black night you saw, Ojeda.
阿吉拉尔扛起了刺客的大旗
Aguilar took up the Assassins' cause.
你经常外出吗?
Do you go out much?
比你勤
More than you.
这里的其他人呢? 他们都是小白鼠吗?
And the others in here? Are they the lab rats too?
他们都是刺客、杀人犯  像他们的祖先一样
They are Assassins, murderers like their ancestors.
像你一样卡尔
Like you, Cal.
都生来带有暴力倾向
All born with predisposition to violence.
杀人犯?
Murderer?
- 你杀了人了 - 一个皮条客
- You killed the man. - A pimp.
你还会杀人么?
Would you kill again?
快乐的一家
Happy families.
她一定非常自豪
She must be very proud.
我怎么知道
I wouldn't know.
她死于刺客之手
She was killed by an Assassin.
像你母亲一样
Like your mother.
抱歉
Sorry.
我老爹杀了我母亲
My old man killed my mother.
你对此有何感受?
And how does that make you feel?
感觉和杀死他一样
Like killing him.
要么我们任其影响我们的余生
Either we let it to effect us for the rest of our lives,
要么我们做点什么
or we just do something about it.
你投向了暴力 我投向了科学
You turn to violence, I turn to science.
这是伊甸苹果卡尔
It's the Apple of Eden, Cal.
我相信它存在
I believe it exists.
圣经告诉我们它包含着 人类第一次反抗的种子
The Bible tells us it contained the seed of man's first disobedience.
但我们中部分人相信
But there are those of us who believe that
神或某种古代文明
God or some ancient civilization
留给了我们一个路线图来 了解为什么人类如此暴力
have left us a road map to understand why people are violent.
阿吉拉尔是我们所知的 最后一个拥有伊甸苹果的人
Aguilar was the last person known to have had it in his possession.
我们需要你找出他把它藏在哪里了
We need you to find out where he hid it.
我以为我是来接受治疗的
I thought I was here to be cured.
暴力就是种疾病
Violence is a disease.
像癌症一样
Like cancer.
并且像癌症一样 我们希望有一天能治愈它
And like cancer, we hope to control it one day.
是暴力让我还活着
Violence is what kept me alive.
好吧 严格地说你死了
Well technically, you're dead.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
我有什么好处?
What's in it for me?
一旦我的研究完成 这里就不需要你了
Once my research is complete, there is no reason to keep you here.
我能回到自己的生活?
I get my life back?
比那更好你将有个新生活
Better. A new one.
你不是饿了么
You are hungry.
你不知道他是谁 他是干什么的
You don't know who he is, what he is.
他是个危险人物
He is a dangerous man.
多给他点时间埃米尔
Give him little more time, Emir.
他或许能证明他的骨子里流着高贵的血
Man may prove that has some noble blood in him yet.
坐这里怎么样先生?
How about, sir?
可以随便点菜 但我们推荐鸡
It's an open menu, but we do recommend a chicken.
你想要点什么 林奇先生? 可以随便点菜
What can I get you, Mr. Lynch? It's an open menu,
但我们推荐鸡
but we do recommend a chicken.
我要牛排
I'll steak.
给开拓者一份牛排
Steak for the pioneer.
你是谁?
Who are you?
他们叫我穆萨
They call me Moussa.
但我的名字是巴普蒂斯特 我已经死了200年了
But my name is Baptiste. I'm dead 200 years now.
伏都毒师
Voodoo poisoner.
我不会伤害任何人
I'm harmless.
他们在盯着你
They're watching you.
等着发现你是谁开拓者
Waiting to see who you are, pioneer.
你见过他了么?
Have you met him yet?
你有没有见过他?
我们都是最后保护伊甸苹果的人我的朋友
We are the last to protect the Apple, my friend.
做错一个选择 你将把我们都送入无底深渊
Pick the wrong choice, you'll send us all to infinity.
这个
This...
是你的
belongs to you.
你将把他们直接引向它
You're going to lead them right to it.
不我打算吃了它
Ne, I'm going to eat it.
什么鬼?
What the fuck is going on?
他必须回到Animus
He has to go back in the Animus.
现在
Now.
在再次进入之前他还需要点时间
He needs more time before he goes in again.
我们没时间了
We don't have time.
为什么?
Why?
我不会拿他的命冒险
I won't risk his life.
那么我就找其他人来做
Then I'll have to find someone else to do it.
- 该你上了高手 - 我已经疯了
- You're up, slugger. - I'm crazy.
我已经疯了
I'm crazy.
因感到寂寞而疯
Crazy for feeling so lonely.
他们又让他进去了
They're getting him back in again.
我们必须在他背叛我们之前阻止他
We should stop him before he betrays us.
日期调到6
Set the date for the six.
如果他状态恶化 就拉他出来
If his condition deteriorates, pull him out.
- 你父亲 - 我不管我爸说了什么
- You father... - I don't care what my father said.
我在世上到底做了什么?
What in the world did I do?
- 卡尔听我说 - 我为尝试疯狂
- Cal, listen to me. - I'm crazy for trying...
听我说 你必须紧盯着阿吉拉尔
Listen to me. You have to stay with Aguilar.
为哭泣疯狂
Crazy for crying...
呆在同步空白处很危险
Staying in synch-void could be dangerous.
我为爱你而疯狂
And I'm crazy for loving you...
很快他们将进军格拉纳德
Soon they will march on Granada.
苏丹穆罕穆德已经虚弱了
Sultan Muhammad is weak.
他将交出伊甸苹果
He'll surrender the Apple
并且为了救王子背叛信条
and betray the Creed to save the prince.
爱让我们变弱
The love makes us weak.
值得高兴的是我将牺牲我的血肉
Gladly I'll sacrifice my flesh and blood,
让信条得以幸存
for survival of the Creed.
当我今天死去时 别为我浪费眼泪
When I die today, don't waste your tears for me.
主发话了
The Lord spoke.
他说:
And he said:
"如果一个人不遵从我
"If a man abide not in me
他就会被投入火中
he is cast into the fire
并且被烧死!"
and he is burned!"
数十年来
For decades,
你们因宗教不同
you have lived in the world torn apart
生活在四分五裂的世界
by religious discord.
但很快感谢上帝
But soon, thanks to God
和宗教法庭
and Inquisition
我们将清洗这一疾病!
we will purge this disease!
你们面前的这些罪人
The sinners before you,
在这场圣战中致力于保护
sought to defend the heretic prince of Granada,
野蛮人最后的据点格拉纳德
the last heathen stronghold
的异教徒的王子
in our holy war.
所以今天
So today,
在我们的国王及皇后面前
before our king and queen
我发誓我将在上帝的圣火中
I swear we shall wash ourselves clean,
净化我们自己!
in the holy fire of God!
看啊
Behold...
上帝的意志!
God's will!
你将看着你们的导师被烧死 然后以最慢的方式死去
You will watch your mentor burn and then you will die the slowest.
给未来带来荣耀
Give glory to the future.
而不是给我们
Not to us.
他正在同步
He is synchronizing.
该死的异教徒!
Damned heretics!
别让他们跑了!
Don't let them escape!
跳
Jump.
同步消除完毕
Complete desynch.
放他下来!
Get him down!
叫医生!
Call the medics!
没事了没事了 卡尔醒醒卡尔
Okay. It's okay. Cal, stay with me. Cal.
稳住 没事了 快点!
Stay... It's okay. Hurry up!
好了好了 看着我
Okay. Okay. Look at me.
看着我
Look at me.
我的腿没知觉了
I can't feel my legs.
瘫痪是暂时的
Paralysis is temporal.
坏消息呢?
What's the bad news?
它造成了神经分裂  但是我们带你挺过来了
It caused a neurological split but we got you through it.
这一次
This time.
我会死在这儿对吧?
I'm gonna die in here, aren't I?
不会
No.
只要你自愿进入那里就不会死
Not if you go in there on your own free will.
我办不到
I can't do this.
不你行的
Yes, you can.
那个伊甸苹果你是仅存的能找到它的人
The Apple. You're the only one left who can find it.
我们能结束这些痛苦卡尔
We can put an end to pain, Cal.
为所有人
For everyone.
你从哪儿得到它的?
Where did you get this?
我父亲从你母亲的谋杀现场取来的
My father recovered it from the scene of your mother's murder.
并带到这里保管
And brought it here for safekeeping.
保管?
Safekeeping?
你偷了它
You stole it.
这是你母亲的项链 我希望你拿着它
It's your mother's necklace. I wanted you to have it.
他为什么在这?
Why was he there?
- 为了救她 - 从谁手里?
- To save her. - From whom?
- 她自己的人 - 和你有什么关系?
- Her own people. - What's that got to do with you?
刺客和圣殿骑士的战争 持续了几个世纪了
Assassins and Templars have been at war for centuries.
我想改变它
I aim to change that.
哦对我忘了
That's right, I forgot.
我们是来和侵略作斗争的
We're here to combat aggression.
我不喜欢你的方法
I don't think I like your methods.
我是科学家
I am a scientist.
我是来治疗暴力的
I'm here to be cured of violence.
谁来治愈你?
Who's gonna cure you?
我们在喂养野兽
We're feeding the beast.
我们在使他变得更强
We're making him stronger.
我是莱金博士
I am Dr Rikkin.
艾伦
Alan.
我在阿布斯泰戈这里负责照看一些事物
I look after things here in Abstergo.
你喜欢把事物 放在一个大家庭里是吧?
You like to keep the things in the family, huh?
是的
Yes.
很抱歉让你感到不舒服
I'm sorry if we caused you any discomfort.
我还能为你做什么?
Is there anything I can do?
放了我怎么样?
How about you let me out of here?
这我办不到
That's something I can't manage.
我是来做交易的
I'm here to make a deal.
我们需要伊甸苹果
We need the Apple.
需要你为我们找到它
And we need you to get it for us.
你已经和Animus消除同步了
You've been desynching in the Animus.
我们希望你不要这样
We need you not to do that.
把我送回机器里?
Sending me back to the machine?
不 你已经给我们看了我们需要看到的
No, you've already shown us what we needed to see.
那你会放我们走吗?
Will you let us free then?
你想从新来的那里获得什么?
What do you hope to gain from the newcomer?
一些有益我们所有人的东西
Something that'll benefit us all.
还有你穆萨
You too, Moussa.
你对他们做了什么?
What have you done to them?
当你不是自愿回到过去时就会这样
It's what happens if you don't enter in regression on your own volition.
你认出这个了吗?
Do you recognize this?
这是刺客的袖剑
It's Assassin's blade.
这就是那把
This is the actual one...
你父亲用来杀死你母亲的刀
your father used to take your mother's life.
他也在这你知道吗?
He's here, you know?
母亲的死卡尔
Mother's death, Cal.
可不是什么应该让孩子看到的东西
Not something a boy should ever be made to see.
这是错的
This is wrong.
你逼我的
You left me no choice.
他必须以自己的意志进入你说的
He has to go in on his own free will, you said that.
- 我必须协商 - 你是说操控?
- I had to negotiate. - You mean manipulate?
我向长老保证我们会为伦敦获得伊甸苹果
I assured the Elders we would have the Apple for London.
在两天内
That's in two days.
他不想知道他的过去 或他父亲的
He doesn't want to know his past, or his father.
他想摧毁他们全部
He wants to destroy them, both.
我们不是来制造怪物的
We're not in the business of creating monsters.
我们既不会制造他们也不会毁灭他们
We neither created them nor destroyed them.
我们只不过任他们沉溺于 自己不可动摇的信仰
We merely abandoned them to their own inexorable faith.
- 你是你母亲的儿子 - 什么意思?
- You're your mother's son. - What does that mean?
你体内流动的血不只是你自己的
Blood that flows through you is not your own.
还属于信条
Belongs to the Creed.
你母亲知道的
Your mother knew that.
她死了信条才得以存活
She died so the Creed may live.
告诉我为什么会这样!
Remind me how, exactly!
你看到的确实是我做的
What you saw, I did.
你谋杀了她
You murdered her.
我宁可夺去她的生命也不想它让机器偷取
I took her life rather than have it stolen by that machine.
使命让人伟大
Man grows with the greatness of his task.
我本应杀了你
I ought to have killed you.
我下不了手
I couldn't.
那么现在
Well, here.
杀了我
Take it.
做你30年前做不了的事
Do what you couldn't do 30 years ago.
刀在你手里卡尔
It's in your hands now, Cal.
这就是他们想要的
This is what they want.
让我留血
Spill my blood.
但是别再回机器里了
But do not go back in the Animus.
为什么?
Why?
伊甸苹果包含了自由意志的基因编码
The Apple contains the genetic code for free will.
他们会用它毁了我们
They will use it to destroy us.
我要找到它
I'm gonna find it.
然后看着他们摧毁你和你的信条
And watch them destroy you and your Creed.
你毁不掉信条
You can not kill the Creed.
它在你的血液里
It's in your blood.
伊甸苹果就是一切
The Apple is everything.
你母亲为保护它而死
Your mother died to protect it.
她没得选
She had no choice.
我有
I do.
你会毁了信条!
You're gonna kill the Creed!
带我去Animus
Take me to the Animus.
把我放进去
Put me in.
准备好Animus
Prepare the Animus.
自愿回归
Voluntary regression.
你知道刺客名字的由来吗?
Do you know how the Assassins came to be named?
来自阿拉伯语 "Hashashin"
From an Arabic word "Hashashin".
他们是被社会排斥的人
They were society's outcasts.
那些冷血偷窃、谋杀的人
Those who stole, who murdered in cold blood.
人们嘲笑他们 叛逆者愚蠢的人瘾君子
People ridiculed them... Rebels, fools, drug addicts.
但他们是智慧的
But they were wise.
他们利用这个名声来向那些甚至最强的敌人
They used this reputation to hide the dedication to principles
隐藏自己所献身原则的
beyond those of even their strongest enemies.
我为此敬佩他们
And for that I admire them.
但你不是其中之一
But you're not one of those men.
那你是吗?
Are you?
走着瞧吧
Let's find out.
启动回归
Commencing regression.
这是我一生的工作
This is my life's work.
这是我的生活
It's my life.
为了信条
For the Creed.
我们的生命
Our own lives...
我们所留下的才是重要的
What matters is what we leave behind.
苏丹
Sultan...
交出伊甸苹果
Surrender the Apple.
你的刺客保护者都没了
Your Assassin protectors are gone.
信条完了
The Creed is finished.
我的孩子
My son.
这里埋藏着
Here lies the seed
人类第一次反抗的种子
of man's first disobedience,
自由意志的种子
of free will itself.
多亏了伊甸苹果
Thanks to the Apple of Eden,
我们所知的世界
the known world
将被领入新时代
shall be ushered into a new age.
一个和平时代
One of peace,
所有战争中的人
in which all the warring populations of mankind
将完全只服从于
shall bow in perfect obedience
我们圣殿骑士的统治
to our one templar rule.
伊甸苹果
The Apple.
给他
Give it to him.
现在
Now.
为了信条
For the Creed.
上!
Go!
原谅我
Forgive me.
结束了!
It's over!
刺客!
Assassin!
信仰之跃
A leap of faith.
我们在哪儿?
Where are we?
看起来像军港
It looks like a military port.
卡的斯帕洛斯-德拉弗龙特拉
Kadiz, Palos de la Frontera.
刺客为它而死
The Assassins died for it.
用你的生命保护它
Protect it with your life.
我是信条的朋友
I am a friend of the Creed.
把它带入你的坟墓
Take it to your grave.
我发誓
I swear.
这是什么? 翻译
What is it? Translation.
循着阳光 我将抛下这旧世界
Following the light of the sun, I shall leave this old world behind.
是克里斯托弗·哥伦布
It's Christopher Columbus.
他被埋在哪儿?
Where is he buried?
他的遗体回到了西班牙
His remains were returned to Spain.
他的陵墓在塞维利亚大教堂
His tomb is in Seville Cathedral.
我们找到它了
We found it.
嘿全明星过来
Hey All Stars, come here.
挑一个
Pick one.
随便哪个
Anyone.
- 公共休息室被突破 - 封锁Animus
- Breach in common room. - Seal the Animus.
这是记忆么?
Is it a memory?
不是
No.
来吧!
Come on!
- 转运? - 准备就绪了
- Transport? - Standing by.
保护Animus 清理整个设施
Protect the Animus. Purge the facility.
我要先带你离开这儿
I need to get you out of here first.
- 不! - 我们必须离开索菲亚
- No! - We have to leave, Sophia.
不!
No!
把它捡起来!
Pick it up!
你不是孤军奋战卡尔
You are not alone, Cal.
你从来不是
You never were.
- 打开 - 来吧
- Open... - Come on.
其他人盲目 追寻真理的时候
Where other men blindly follow the truth,
- 记住 - 万事皆虚
- remember... - Nothing is true.
当其他人被 道德法律束缚时
Where other men are limited by morality or law,
- 记住 - 事事皆允
- remember... - Everything is permitted.
我们在黑暗中为光明服务
We work in the darkness to serve the light.
我们是刺客
We are Assassins.
现在怎么办 开拓者?
What now, pioneer?
我们打
We fight.
阁下
Your Excellency.
荣耀属于你父亲
The glory will go to your father.
但我们都知道是谁发现了它
But we both know who found it.
属于你的时刻回来的孩子
Your time will come, my child.
圣殿骑士圣堂 伦敦
GREAT TEMPLAR LODGE, LONDON P s a g m e n o .com
他们会因此给你个诺贝尔和平奖
They'll give you a Nobel peace prize for this.
你最好开始写演讲稿
You better start writing your speech.
- 我读了你的 - 然后呢?
- I've read yours. - And?
如果我们消灭了自由意志 我们就消灭了刺客
If we eradicate free will, we eradicate the Assassins.
一个威胁了世界几个世纪的癌症
A cancer that has menaced society for centuries.
这不是我最好的作品 但它能表达我的意思
It's not my best work, but it gets the point across.
我们一直在寻找解决途径
We've been looking for solutions.
你已经消除了问题
You've eliminated the problem.
那么我的计划
So my program...
第一次给社会带来秩序
Has brought order to society for the first time.
我对此负责
I'm accountable for this.
你已经尽责了
You've already been accounted for.
我们的成果属于长老
Our work belongs to the Elders.
这是他们最美好的时光
This is their finest hour.
你对我撒谎了
You lied to me.
我一直知道
I've always known
在你心里你永远首先是个科学家 然后才是圣殿骑士
that in your heart you're a scientist first, templar second.
你最近的成果令人刮目相看
Your recent work has impressed as much
但它让我们坚信
but it has confirmed our belief that mankind
人类无法被拯救
cannot be redeemed.
一切都被你料到了
You've thought of everything.
也不尽然我的演讲 需要你优雅的开场白
Not quite. My speech. It could do with one of your elegant openings.
“现在我成了世界的
Now I've become death,
死亡和毁灭者”
the destroyer of worlds.
这好像不行
Not sure that I could make that work.
今晚我很高兴能介绍
It is with great pleasure tonight that I introduce
我们古老教团的未来的建筑师
the architect of our ancient order's future.
请欢迎阿布斯泰戈基金会的CEO
Please welcome the CEO of Abstergo Foundation,
艾伦·莱金博士
Dr. Alan Rikkin.
随着伊甸苹果的发现
With the recovery of the Apple,
我们获得了
we are now in possession
人类本性的
of the complete genetic road map
完整基因路线图
to humanity's instincts.
任何对独立、抵抗、
Any impulse towards independence,
造反的冲动
resistance or rebellion
将被铲除
will be crushed.
任何反抗我们前进步伐的倾向
Any predisposition that might oppose our march of progress
现在都能被消灭
can now be eradicated.
我所需做的就是大叫
All I have to do is shout.
我是来帮你的
I'm here to help you.
你也要帮我
And you're here to help me.
我帮不了你了
I can't help you anymore.
那些伟大的计划呢?
What about all those great plans?
治愈暴力 和侵略作斗争
Cure violence, combat aggression.
那就是马上要发生的
That's not going to happen.
你造成了这一切索菲亚 你逃避不了
You've started this, Sophie. You don't get to walk away.
我们都知道接下来会发生什么
We both know what happens next.
不是所有事物都值得存活
Not everything deserves to live.
我办不到
I can't do this.
不你能行
Yes, you can.
但不是给我们自己
But it is not to ourselves,
而是给未来 我们必须献出荣耀
but to the future, that we must give glory.
一个清除刺客的未来!
A future purged of the Assassin's Creed!
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
伊甸苹果
the Apple of Eden.
是我干的
I did this.
我会为长老们取回神器的
I will retrieve the artifact for the Elders.
我想要抓到林奇
Lynch I want for me.
不是给我们自己
It is not to ourselves,
而是给未来 我们必须献出荣耀
but to the future, that we must give glory.